

Bogoslavskyi I. igor.bogoslavskyi@gmail.com

GitHub::niosus

Facebook::bogoslavskyi +49 (0152) 04471543

# Igor Bogoslavskyi

# **Computer Science Student**

#### About me

I am a young computer science specialist, particularly interested in Robotics and Computer Vision fields of study.

I am fond of the idea of autonomous moving vehicles and look forward to having a chance of facing the problems that arise in this field.

The best way to contact me would be just to send an e-mail.

# **Experience**

#### June 2012 - present, Assistant in HRL lab Albert Ludwigs University of Freiburg, Germany

As an assistant in the Humanoid Robots Lab at Uni Freiburg,
 I dealt with Kinect RGBD sensors mounted onto the NAO robot platform with relation to gesture analysis.

#### January 2012 - present, Assistant in AIS lab Albert Ludwigs University of Freiburg, Germany

 As an assistant in the Autonomous Intelligent Systems lab at Uni Freiburg, I dealt with Kinect RGBD sensors mounted onto various platforms as well as unmounted, with relation to RGBD object segmentation and traversability analysis.

November 2011 - April 2012, Tutor in Image Processing class

#### Albert Ludwigs University of Freiburg, Germany

- As a tutor in the chair of Computer Vision and Image Processing at Uni Freiburg my tasks were to help my fellow students to accomplish the course programming assignments.
- Involved c++ programming with relation to blurring/deblurring, optical flow and segmentation tasks.

## December 2010 - October 2011, Junior Software Developer Timecode LLC, Kyiv, Ukraine

- worked as part of a team on a game for Android platform.
   Involved Java Android programming, OpenGL.
- worked as part of a team on an Online Content Store controlled via Kinect sensor. Mostly finding and fixing bugs. C#.

## **Education**

2011 - present, Albert-Ludwigs-Universitt Freiburg

MSc. Applied Computer Science

2007 - 2011, Kyiv National Taras Shevchenko University

BSc. Faculty of Cybernetics. Applied Math field.

Chair of Computational Methods

2004 - 2007, Lyceum 145, Kyiv

Higher basic education certificate, Mathematics, Physics.

# Languages

- English (IELTS 8.0)
- o German (B2)
- Russian (Native)
- Ukrainian (Native)

## **Skills**

#### Platforms and libraries

ROSOpenNIOpenCVOpenGLAndroidPCL

## **Programming and markup languages**

C++
Python
Xml
Java
Matlab/Octave
SQLite

#### Fields of interest

- Mobile Robotics
- Image Processing
- Kinect
- Computer Vision
- Autonomous Navigation
- SLAM

## **Hobbies**

- Android-programming
- Volleyball
- Playing guitar
- Rock music
- Skiing
- Hiking
- Biking
- New technology
- Learning new stuff

# References

References upon request.